<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Academic Melaka Kini</title>
    <link>%22/%22/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Academic Melaka Kini</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Your Name</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 22:12:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="%22/%22/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>themes that work</title>
      <link>%22/%22/post/themes-that-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 22:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>%22/%22/post/themes-that-work/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to all the hardworking and creative theme makers that post to Hugo.
###shoutout thanks to you guys I get to have nice looking site. Thank you for your efforts I get my thoughts out.
But why?
Why should anyone crack their heads to provide FREE themes to others? Why spend nights perfecting their themes so that others can have beautiful websites?  It&amp;rsquo;s amazing! you guys rock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>success almost</title>
      <link>%22/%22/post/success-almost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 21:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>%22/%22/post/success-almost/</guid>
      <description>Can I shout for joy?
It&amp;rsquo;s almost a success. I&amp;rsquo;ve finally got the website running on appernetic.io and on the most basic amp theme. I&amp;rsquo;ve got the posts appearing on the front page and attempting to make the &amp;ldquo;about&amp;rdquo; sections to show up.
Let&amp;rsquo;s try changing theme. If you can read this then the theme change was successful.
Also trying to move a post from default to go under &amp;ldquo;post&amp;rdquo; directory so that it shows up on front page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>third post</title>
      <link>%22/%22/post/third-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 21:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>%22/%22/post/third-post/</guid>
      <description>No wonder.
Without toml the site won&amp;rsquo;t publish
This is getting chaotic and I&amp;rsquo;m getting no where. These posts were typed on the iPad from the 2nd generation and works fine. No need to install anything it runs off the internet
It&amp;rsquo;s about figuring out how to get the themes going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>third post but not</title>
      <link>%22/%22/post/thirdpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 21:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>%22/%22/post/thirdpost/</guid>
      <description>how Un creative
After the first comes the second and then the third. But this is not good for I have got 1 and 3 but not 2 because I forgot to put it in post directory. So how do I move it?
Hope this is good investment and apprentice thrives.   appernetic has a great concept. It&amp;rsquo;s just that I&amp;rsquo;m still in the process of working out what that is and how to gel with it so that I can get to change theme while learning the ropes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>firstpost</title>
      <link>%22/%22/post/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 09:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>%22/%22/post/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post and i have no clue what so ever what&amp;rsquo;s happening. Been typing the about section and now the first post section and am still wondering what&amp;rsquo;s going to happen to get it to happen. #update Have just seen the youtube &amp;ldquo;silent movie&amp;rdquo; style tutorial and published it but nothing is seen yet. WIll come back and test in 15 mins
Am back and today it&amp;rsquo;s the 28th of April and am not making much progress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>